[
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Where did The Flowerpot Men want to go in 1967?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "New York", 
            "2": "San Francisco",
            "3": "Woodstock",
            "4": "Memphis"
        },
        "correct_answer": 2
    },{
        "id": 66,
        "question": "How many earths would fit inside the sun?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "circa 100", 
            "2": "circa 1,000,000", 
            "3": "circa 10,000",
            "4": "circa 100,000"
        },
        "correct_answer": 2
    },{
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which actor appeared in the Cranberries music video Ridiculous Thought?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "Bruce Willis", 
            "2": "Donald Sutherland", 
            "3": "George Clooney",
            "4": "Elijah Wood"
        },
        "correct_answer": 4
    },{
        "id": 24,
        "question": "In which book is there an inn called Admiral Benbow?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "Lord of the Rings", 
            "2": "Gulliver's Travels", 
            "3": "Treasure Island",
            "4": "Peter Pan"
        },
        "correct_answer": 3
    },{
        "id": 55,
        "question": "What is the name of the man servant in 'Around the world in 80 days'?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "Pas Partout", 
            "2": "Cato", 
            "3": "Giles",
            "4": "Machu Picchu"
        },
        "correct_answer": 1
    },{
        "id": 66,
        "question": "In which film do the words 'I love you' save the planet earth?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "The Day After Tomorrow", 
            "2": "The 5th Element", 
            "3": "Mars Attacks",
            "4": "Independence Day"
        },
        "correct_answer": 2
    },{
        "id": 77,
        "question": "'Goodbye Farewell and Amen' was the final episode of which TV series?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "MASH", 
            "2": "Dallas", 
            "3": "Friends",
            "4": "The muppet show"
        },
        "correct_answer": 2
    },{
        "id": 88,
        "question": "James Bond was searching for what kind of airplane in 'Thunderball'?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "707", 
            "2": "Piper Cub", 
            "3": "Vulkan",
            "4": "B-52"
        },
        "correct_answer": 2
    },{
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which kind of animal did Florence Nightingale often carry around in her pocket?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "Kitten", 
            "2": "Puppy", 
            "3": "Owl",
            "4": "Snake"
        },
        "correct_answer": 3
    },{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who wrote 'don't count your chickens before they are hatched'?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "Aesop", 
            "2": "Shakespeare", 
            "3": "Ben Franklin",
            "4": "Chaucer"
        },
        "correct_answer": 1
    },{
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which NHL hockey team has won the most Stanley Cups?",
        "answers": {
            "1": "Toronto Maple Leafs", 
            "2": "Boston Bruins", 
            "3": "Montreal Canadiens",
            "4": "New York Rangers"
        },
        "correct_answer": 1
    }
]